("SUPER FREAK" BY RICK JAMES)
♪♪♪
♪ SHE'S A VERY KINKY GIRL ♪
♪ THE KIND YOU DON'T
TAKE HOME TO MOTHER ♪
♪ SHE WILL NEVER LET
YOUR SPIRITS DOWN ♪
♪ ONCE YOU GET HER OFF
THE STREET OW GIRL ♪
♪ SHE LIKES THE
BOYS IN THE BAND ♪
♪ SHE SAYS THAT I'M
HER ALL TIME FAVORITE ♪
♪ WHEN I MAKE MY MOVE TO HER
ROOM IT'S THE RIGHT TIME ♪
♪ SHE'S NEVER HARD
TO PLEASE OH NO ♪
♪ THAT GIRL IS PRETTY WILD NOW ♪
♪ THE GIRL'S A SUPER FREAK ♪
♪ THE KIND OF GIRL YOU READ
ABOUT IN NEW WAVE MAGAZINES ♪
♪ THAT GIRL IS PRETTY KINKY
THE GIRL'S A SUPER FREAK ♪
♪ I REALLY LOVE TO TASTE
HER EVERY TIME WE MEET ♪
♪ SHE'S ALRIGHT SHE'S ALRIGHT ♪
♪ THE GIRL'S ALRIGHT ♪
♪ THAT GIRL'S ALRIGHT ♪
♪ WITH ME YEAH HEY HEY HEY HEY ♪
♪ SHE'S A SUPER
FREAK SUPER FREAK ♪
♪ SHE'S SUPER FREAKY
YOW EVERYBODY SING ♪
♪ SUPER FREAK SUPER FREAK ♪
♪ SHE'S A VERY SPECIAL GIRL ♪
♪ THE KIND OF GIRL
YOU WANT TO KNOW ♪
♪ FROM HER HEAD DOWN
TO HER TOENAILS ♪
♪ DOWN TO HER FEET YEAH ♪
♪ AND SHE'LL WAIT FOR ME AT
BACKSTAGE WITH HER GIRLFRIENDS ♪
♪ IN A LIMOUSINE GOING BACK TO ♪
♪ CHINATOWN ♪
♪ THREE'S NOT A CROWD ♪
♪ TO HER SHE'S SAYS
MANAGE A TROIS ♪
♪ OO LA LA ♪
♪ ROOM 714 I'LL BE WAITING ♪
♪ WHEN I GET THERE SHE'S GOT
INCENSE WINE AND CANDLES ♪
♪ IT'S A SUCH A FREAKY SCENE ♪
♪ THAT GIRL IS PRETTY KINKY
THE GIRL'S A SUPER FREAK ♪
♪ THE KIND OF GIRL YOU READ
ABOUT IN NEW WAVE MAGAZINES ♪
♪ THAT GIRL IS PRETTY WILD NOW ♪
♪ THE GIRL'S A SUPER FREAK ♪
♪ I REALLY LIKE TO TASTE
HER EVERY TIME WE MEET ♪
♪ SHE'S ALRIGHT SHE'S ALRIGHT ♪
♪ THE GIRL'S ALRIGHT ♪
♪ WITH ME YEAH HEY HEY HEY HEY ♪
♪ SHE'S A SUPER FREAK SUPER
FREAK SHE'S SUPER FREAKY YOW ♪
♪ TEMPTATIONS SING ♪
♪ OH OH OH OH OH OH OH OH OH ♪
♪ SUPER FREAK SUPER FREAK
THAT GIRL'S A SUPER FREAK ♪
♪ OH OH OH OH OH OH OH ♪
♪ SHE'S A VERY KINKY GIRL ♪
♪ THE KIND YOU WON'T
TAKE HOME TO MOTHER ♪
♪ AND SHE WILL NEVER
LET YOUR SPIRITS DOWN ♪
♪ ONCE YOU GET HER
OFF THE STREET ♪
♪ BLOW DANNY ♪
♪♪♪
♪ OH GIRL ♪